(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-09-11T03:40:47.328699",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
lucid dream
[Title: Lucid Dream]
ヒトリ
[Song: Hitori]
愛されないことは
That I wouldn't be loved...
私が一番知っていたの
...was something I knew best of all.
それでもあなたはこの痛みに
Even so, you still gave...
意味を与えてくれたから
...meaning to this pain.
壊れてしまう恋だとしても
Even if it was a love destined to break...
信じた人と思えた
...I could still believe you were the one.
...たんだよ
...I was.
あなたなら私のすべて
I felt that you, of all people,
わかってくれる気がした
would understand everything about me.
あなたを愛しすぎてしまう前に
Before I end up loving you too much,
あなたをすべて知る前に
Before I get to know everything about you,
空に願う 遠く未来があるように
I pray to the sky that we'll have a distant future.
今もそう 独り 泣いてるの
Even now, yes, I'm crying all alone.
小さな私の手に挟まれた
Held between my small hands...
あなたの大きくて
...was your big hand.
失いたくないと願うほど苦しくなっていたの
The more I wished not to lose it, the more painful it became.
首についた真っ赤な愛が消える前にあなたに会いたくて
Before the crimson mark of love on my neck disappears, I wanted to see you.
目を閉じると巻き戻される最後の温かい夜
When I close my eyes, that last warm night rewinds in my mind.
優しいその目と優しいその声と言葉すべて嘘じゃないと言い聞かせて
Telling myself that those gentle eyes, voice, and words weren't all a lie.
これで最後の恋だと思うのだから繋ぎ止めていたかったのに
Because I thought this would be my last love, I wanted to hold onto you, and yet...
もうすべてわかってるから もう私に近寄らないでよ
Because I already understand everything, don't come near me anymore.
果てしないこの苦しみまでも愛せるほど強い人はいないから
Because no one is strong enough to love even this endless suffering.
あなたを愛しているから ずっとあなたが私を忘れるまで
Because I love you, until you forget about me forever,
星に願う どうか行かないで ずっと私のそばにいてほしい
I pray to the stars, please don't go, I want you to be by my side forever.
あなたを愛しすぎてしまう前に
Before I end up loving you too much,
あなたをすべて知る前に
Before I get to know everything about you,
空に願う 遠く未来があるように
I pray to the sky that we'll have a distant future.
今もそう 独り 泣いてるの
Even now, yes, I'm crying all alone.
Lagu Tanpa Huruf R
[Title: A Song Without the Letter R]
Ini kisahnya anak manusia
This is the story of a human child
Kau bisa memanggilnya dengan nama Iofi
You can call her by the name of Iofi
Sebuah konsonan yang menyulitkan
A difficult consonant
Membuat lidahnya bosan tak bisa ucapkan
Makes her tongue tired, unable to pronounce it
Dia coba pahami
She tries to understand
Setiap manusia
Each and every human
Punya hebat punya cacat
Has their strengths, has their flaws
Punya hebat, punya cacat
With strengths and flaws
Dia coba nikmati hidup ini cuma sekali
She tries to enjoy this life which only comes once
Dia
She
Hanya punya modal cinta
Only has love to offer
Yang dia embuskan dalam setiap iganya
Which she breathes with every rib
Tak inginkan semua tuk suka
She doesn't expect everyone to like her
Dia
She
Hanya ingin tuliskan lagu
Only wants to write songs
Tentang semua yang ada dalam hatinya
About everything inside her heart
Bila tak suka tentu saja tak mengapa
If you don't like it, of course that's fine
Sejak kecil dia punya mimpi
Ever since she was little, she had a dream
Jadi musisi atau apapun di bidang seni
To be a musician or anything in the arts
Tumbuh dewasa bulatlah sudah
As she grew up, her mind was set
Keputusannya tuk dapatkan mimpinya
On her decision to achieve her dream
Dia coba pahami setiap manusia
She tries to understand every human
Punya hebat, punya cacat
With strengths and flaws
Dia coba nikmati hidup ini cuma sekali
She tries to enjoy this life which only comes once
Dia
She
Hanya punya modal cinta
Only has love to offer
Yang dia embuskan dalam setiap iganya
Which she breathes with every rib
Tak inginkan semua tak suka
She doesn't want everyone to dislike her
Dia
She
Hanya ingin tuliskan lagu
Only wants to write songs
Tentang semua yang ada dalam hatinya
About everything inside her heart
Bila tak suka tentu saja tak mengapa
If you don't like it, of course that's fine
Dia
She
Hanya punya modal cinta
Only has love to offer
Yang dia embuskan dalam setiap lagunya
Which she breathes with every song of hers
Tak inginkan semua tuk suka
She doesn't expect everyone to like her
Dia
She
Hanya ingin tuliskan lagu
Only wants to write songs
Tentang semua yang ada dalam hatinya
About everything inside her heart
Bila tak suka tentu saja tak mengapa
If you don't like it, of course that's fine
Hanya punya modal cinta
Only has love to offer
Yang dia embuskan dalam setiap lagunya
Which she breathes with every song of hers
Tak inginkan semua tak suka
She doesn't want everyone to dislike her
Dia
She
Hanya ingin tuliskan lagu
Only wants to write songs
Tentang semua yang ada dalam hatinya
About everything inside her heart
Bila tak suka tentu saja tak mengapa
If you don't like it, of course that's fine
Ioforia, Obisa, halo!
Ioforia, Obisa, hello!
Aku Airani Iofifteen, Iofi dari Hololive Indonesia First Generation, halo! Selamat datang di Birthday Live!
I'm Airani Iofifteen, Iofi from Hololive Indonesia 1st Gen! Hello, and welcome to my Birthday Live!
And by the way, the hashtag is #iofiLucidDream, you can just tweet all of you can, okay?
And by the way, the hashtag is #iofiLucidDream. Please tweet as much as you can, okay?
And by the way, 気づいてる人もいると思うんだけど、あのさっきの曲「R」がないんですよ、はい。
And by the way, some of you might have noticed, but that song doesn't contain the letter "R" at all!
There is no R whatsoever.
Jadi kalian kalau misalkan kalian sama cadel kayak aku, kalian bisa nyanyi lagu ini karena gak ada R-nya.
So if you also have a lisp like me, you can sing this song because it doesn't have the letter R!
Tapi bagi yang gak nge... apa ya? Bagi yang gak nyadar, nanti akan keluar versi cover song-nya.
But for those who didn't... what is it? For those who didn't notice, a cover version will be released later!
そのカバー曲のバージョンもあるので、後でまた見てね。はい、there will be a cover song.
The cover song version is also coming out, so make sure to check it out later! Yes, there will be a cover song.
And by the way, by the way, this guitar...
実はね、家でもさ、このモデルとこの色のギターもあるんですよ。合ってみてください、はい。
Actually, I have a guitar with the exact same model and color at home. Please look for it, yes.
And if you remember, I kind of like uploaded this guitar picture somewhere. Yes.
And if you remember, I kind of uploaded a picture of this guitar somewhere. Yes.
Tapi biasanya aku main gitar cuma di membership. Iya, jadi ini pertama kalinya aku main gitar selain di membership. Mmhmm, I usually play guitar like around in membership.
But usually, I only play guitar in membership streams. So this is the first time I'm playing guitar outside of membership. Mmhmm, I usually play guitar around in membership.
Yes, yes, yes.
そう。あの、メン限のみんなはもう知ってると思いますけど
Right. I think everyone in my membership already knows this, but...
あの、普通はギターのメン限でしか弾いてないんだけど、これが
Normally, I only play the guitar in membership-only streams, but this...
メン限じゃない配信で初めてです！
is the first time in a public stream!
いや、ちょっと怖いんだけど。もう、まあまあまあ、どうでしたか？
I was a bit scared, but... Well, how was it?
どう？どう？可愛い？可愛い？いっぱいスクショ撮った？スクショ撮った？
How was it? Is it cute? Did you take lots of screenshots?
I hope you enjoyed it!
And by the way, we still have a lot of more going on.
And by the way, we still have a lot more going on!
So after this, there's going to be a lot and a lot of guests!
So please wait for it.
この後もゲストが盛りだくさんなので、楽しみにしててくだいさいね！
We have lots of guests coming up after this, so please look forward to it!
Don't forget to take a lot of screenshot!
Don't forget to take a lot of screenshots!
可愛い？らぎ？らぎ？らちゅ？らちゅ？らちゅ？らちゅ？
Cute? Ragi? Ragi? Rachu? Rachu? Rachu? Rachu?
まあね、時間があればこれもね、またギター弾きたいなと思っております。はい！
Well, if there's time, I'd love to play the guitar again. Yes!
あ、オッケー？準備オッケー？オッケー、オッケー、オッケー。オッケー？うん。
Oh, okay? Ready? Okay, okay, okay. Okay? Yes.
あ、オッケー！スタッフ（笑）
Ah, okay! Staff, haha!
では！ゲストパートにまた会おうね！Thank you! See you guys in guest part!
Well then! See you again in the guest segment! Thank you! See you guys in the guest part!
どこから話せばいいんだろう
Where should I start talking from?
待ちくたびれても
Even if I'm tired of waiting...
終わりだなんて言わせないから
...I won't let anyone say it's the end.
書き殴った無意識の衝動をつれて<
With the unconscious impulse scribbled down,
何もかも壊したら
once we destroy everything...
不可能を始めればいいんだ
...we can start the impossible.
There's a reason that we came across in this world
There's a reason that we caught the magnetic wave
傷つけ合う世界はどこへ
Where is this mutually-hurting world headed?
そう 愛のために泣けるのは 君がそこにいるから
Yes, the reason I can cry for love is because you are there.
君だけを呼び続けるから
Because I will keep calling out only to you.
愛のために歌うのは そして共に生き抜くこと
The reason I sing for love is to survive together with you...
ずっと 君と
...forever, by your side.
青色した空と 波ひとつない鏡のような海を見てた
I was watching the blue sky and the mirror-like sea, completely still.
どんな場所にいたって どんな形になって どんな時代にいたって
No matter where we are, no matter what form we take, no matter what era we live in,
見つけだす
I will find you...
宙吊りにした運命に逆らって
...defying this suspended fate.
There's a reason that we came across in this world
There's a reason that we caught the magnetic wave
引き寄せ合う二人はどこへ
Where are the two of us, drawn together, headed?
そう 愛のために進むのは 君とここにいるから
Yes, the reason I move forward for love is because I am here with you.
僕だけが君を護るから
Because I alone will protect you.
愛のために願うのは そして誰も傷つけずに
What I wish for love is to hurt absolutely no one...
ずっと 隣で
...forever, by your side.
僕らは超えてゆく すべての憎しみを
We will overcome all hatred.
ニセモノの正義など捨ててしまえ保存
Throw away things like fake justice.
そう 愛のために泣けるのは 君がそこにいるから
Yes, the reason I can cry for love is because you are there...
We will always be together
We'll always be together...
愛の...
Of love...
愛のために進むのは
The reason I move forward for love...
君とここにいるから
Is because I am here with you.
僕だけが
Because only I...
君を守るから
will protect you.
愛のために願うのは
The reason I wish for love...
そして共に生き抜く事
Is to survive together.
ずっと
Always...
We'll always be together.
よっぴー、お誕生日おめでとう！
Yoppy, happy birthday!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
いや、やった、今年も来てくれてありがとう。
Yay! Thank you for coming again this year.
いぇーい！どうもこんにちは、ときのそらです。
Yay! Hello everyone, I'm Tokino Sora.
よろしくお願いします、こっちだ。
Nice to meet you! Over here.
いや、なんかバラード歌っちゃったね。
Man, we ended up singing a ballad.
ねー。
Yeah.
より、私すごい気になってるんだけど、なんなん、これ？
But I'm really curious... What is this?
宇宙、超寒いから、これ温かいよ。
Space is super cold, so this is warm.
えっ、宇宙で焚き火なんてできるんだね。
Wait, you can have a campfire in space?
できるよ、一応。
You can, actually.
だって、酸素があるってことだ…あっ、でも…
That means there's oxygen... Oh, but...
でも酸素いるからさ、今、これバリアいるからさ。
But since we need oxygen, we have this barrier right now.
あ、バリアあるからね。酸素ないから…ないんだったらもう耐えられないじゃん。
Ah, because of the barrier. Without oxygen, we wouldn't survive.
あ、そうそう、そうだね。
Ah, right, exactly.
うん、そう。温かくて良いね。
Yeah, it's nice and warm.
MCでこんなにまったり、焚き火の前で、こう、なんか夜のなんか二人で喋っちゃうみたいな雰囲気でやる事ないよ。
We've never done an MC like this, so relaxed in front of a campfire, like two people talking late at night.
ないから、ちょっと変な感じがする。
It feels a bit strange because of that.
あ、そうだね。普通にさ、ポーズした後に、こう「はぁ、やっと会えたね」という感じでいいんじゃない？
Oh, true. Usually, we strike a pose and then go, "Haa, we finally met!"
すぐだけど、やっぱり今年のテーマはもっとゆるいとか、落ち着く雰囲気ほしいから。
But since this year's theme is more relaxed and cozy...
そのダンスとあの歌のあとに、一応マイクをね、ちょっと落としてここに座ってるっていうね。
After the dancing and singing, we put down our mics and sit here.
でも良いね、なんかまったりできるから、ちょっとのんびりしておしゃべりできる感じ、良いと思う、すごく。
But it's nice. Since we can relax and chat leisurely, I really like this vibe.
やった、やった。
Yay, awesome.
でね、今年、誕生日に、2回くらいなんだよね、毎年。そう、今年…ん？去年も。
And you know, we've done this on my birthday about twice now, every year. Wait, last year too...
あ、去年と一常年ってこと？
Ah, you mean last year and the year before?
そうそうそう。今年、で、来年も来る？
Yes, yes! And this year. Will you come next year too?
え、もちろんもちろん！呼んでもらえればいつでも行くよ。
Of course! If you invite me, I'll always come.
お、やったー！
Oh, yay!
じゃ、決定！
Then it's decided!
やったー！わーい！
Yay! Woohoo!
そしたら、なんか、もうこの、去年と今年とも、こうハンドマイクであのやってるから。
Since we've been using hand mics both last year and this year...
そうだね。なんか結構、聴かせるみたいな感じの曲だったよね。
True. The songs were really meant for listening.
そう、じゃあ来年はバリバリ踊ります？そしたら。
Right. So, should we dance like crazy next year?
あ、踊る！
Oh, let's dance!
いいね、踊りやっぱり姉さん好き？踊るの。
Nice. Do you really love dancing, Sis?
うん、大好き！よっぴーは？
Yeah, I love it! What about you, Yoppy?
好き好き好き！
I love it, love it, love it!
ねー、いいよねー。いや、でもなんか、今年のテーマさっきも聞いて「バラード」だって聞いて。
Right? It's great. When I heard this year's theme was "ballad"...
やっぱさ、バラードのさ、全体をさ、ライブするのってすごい難しいなって私は思っちゃうの。
I personally think it's really hard to do an entire live show with ballads.
え、そうなの？
Oh, really?
やっぱ、演出とかもそうだけどさ、私はいつもダンスとかで見せるみたいなのをやるから。
Like, the staging is one thing, but I usually perform by showing off dancing.
バラードで挑戦するのってすごいなって思ってたんだよね。
So I thought challenging yourself with ballads was really amazing.
あー、そっか。でもなんか自分にとってはバラードが一番声に似合うから。
Ah, I see. But for me, ballads fit my voice the best.
そう、なんか、もっと見せたいなとは思ってて。
Yeah, so I wanted to showcase that more.
あ、そっか。
Ah, I see.
そう、だからね…お、ほら見える、いっぱい。うわー！
Yeah, so... Oh, look, there are so many of them. Wow!
綺麗！宇宙！
Beautiful! Space!
宇宙に来ました。なんか去年もちょっと…
We've come to space. We did a bit of this last year too...
一応は宇宙にいたんだけど。
We were technically in space then too.
あんまり見えないかもしれない、それは。だから今年はちゃんと宇宙に行きたいですって言って。
But maybe you couldn't really see it. So this year, I said I wanted to properly go to space!
わー、すごい！宇宙来ました、二人で。
Wow, amazing! We came to space together.
あ、綺麗、本当に。
Ah, it's really beautiful.
お、なんか姉さんと似合うんじゃない？
Oh, doesn't it really suit you, Sis?
本当？
Really?
そう、なんか普通にイメージカラーが青だから。
Yeah, since your image color is blue.
ねー。
Yeah.
みんなもいっぱいスクショ撮った？
Did you all take lots of screenshots?
撮った！ / 撮った！
We did! / We did!
似合うでしょ？ほら、めっちゃ可愛い。ぱちぱちして！
Does it suit me? Look, it's so cute. Blink!
おー！あはははは！
Oh! Ahahaha!
可愛い！ / おっ！
So cute! / Oh!
もっと見せて！あ、あ！
Show me more! Ah, ah!
って、これは私の記念日じゃないんだ
Wait, this isn't my anniversary stream.
そうそう！ / よっぴー！よっぴー！
That's right! / Yoppi! Yoppi!
いい、大丈夫だよ。はい、いっぱい撮りました。二人で。
It's fine, it's okay. Alright, we took lots of pictures together.
ういー！ / ういー！
Wheee! / Wheee!
はい、ということでね。今回はまだまだあるので、皆様も楽しみにしてください。
So, there's still more to come today, so please look forward to it!
ね、本当におめでとう！
Yes, congratulations, really!
では、来年また歌って踊ろうね。 / 踊ろう！
Let's sing and dance together again next year. / Let's dance!
はい、じゃあ皆さんありがとう！ / ありがとうございました！
Alright, thank you, everyone! / Thank you so much!
まったねー！ / まったねー！
See you! / See you!
何度も 問いかけた
I asked myself so many times...
自問自答 繰り返した先に
...through all the soul-searching, in the end.
答えが あるのなら
If there is indeed an answer...
このまま 探してみようか
...should we keep on searching like this?
あなたの未来図に
In your map of the future...
私は少しでも入れたかな
...did I even find a tiny place?
あなたのいない世界は
A world without you here...
想像さえつかなかった
...was something I couldn't even imagine.
もしもあなたが
If only you...
あの子を選んだ瞬間に
...choose her at that exact moment...
私が頭の中
...what was running through...
駆け巡っていたなら
...my head back then...
悔しいな
...makes me feel so frustrated.
こんなにも あなたのこと
Even though I love you this much...
好きになってしまう前に
...before falling for you...
せめてさ サヨナラの言葉
...I wish you would have at least...
告げて欲しかったなんて
...given me a proper goodbye.
勝手なわがままだよね<
That's just my selfish wish, isn't it?
誰より 思っているのに
Even though I care for you more than anyone...
あなたを世界で一番
...the one who can make you smile...
笑顔に 変えられる
...the most in this whole world...
人はきっと 私じゃないから
...is definitely not me.
どうか 幸せになって
So please, be happy.
どんな未来があっても
No matter what kind of future lies ahead...
変わりはしないこの現実が
...this reality that will never change...
ただただ 目の前の
...simply takes away...
光すべて 奪い去った
...every single light from before my eyes.
生まれ変わっても
Even if I am reborn...
もう一度あなたに恋するかな
...would I fall in love with you once again?
そんな妄想なんて
Such a delusion...
考えることすらも
...even just thinking about it...
馬鹿みたい
...is so foolish.
こんなにも あなたのこと
Even though I love you this much...
好きになってしまう前に
...before falling for you...
わざとさ
...you purposely...
優しい言葉で 勘違いさせないでって
...shouldn't have misled me with kind words.
勝手なわがままだよね
That's just my selfish wish, isn't it?
あなたの幸せそうな
Just looking at...
顔を見るだけで 胸いっぱいになる
...your happy face fills my heart completely.
あなたと私はきっと
You and I are surely...
お似合いじゃないから
...not meant to be together.
どうか 幸せになって
So please, be happy.
涙出るのは
The reason my tears flow...
嘘でも 強がるから
...is because I'm pretending to be strong, even if it's a lie.
気付かないフリしないで
Please don't pretend not to notice.
どうしても 諦められないよ
No matter what, I just can't give up on you...
終わった恋なのに
...even though our love is already over.
こんなにも あなたのこと...
Even though I love you this much...
好きになってしまう前に
Before I end up falling in love with you,
せめてさ
At least...
サヨナラの言葉つけててほしかったなって
I wish you had given me a word of goodbye.
勝手でワガママだよね
I know it's selfish and willful of me.
こんなにも あなたのこと
Even though I...
好きになってしまう前に
fell so deeply in love with you...
せめてさ
At least...
サヨナラの言葉つけててほしかったなって
I wish you had given me a word of goodbye.
勝手でワガママだよね
I know it's selfish and willful of me.
誰よりも想ってるのに
Even though I care about you more than anyone else,
あなたを世界で
the one who can make you smile the most...
一番笑顔に
in this world...
変えられるのはきっと
is surely...
私じゃないから
not me.
幸せになって
Please be happy.
わー！二人とも来てくれてありがとう！
Wow! Thank you both so much for coming!
誕生日おめでとう！
Happy birthday!
ありがとう！嬉しい！
Thank you! I'm so happy!
イェーイ！
Yay!
嬉しい！ありがとう！おめでとう！
I'm so happy! Thank you! / Congratulations!
でも最初は、誰から自己紹介する？
But first, who should introduce themselves first?
んじゃ俺からいこうかな？
Then, how about I go first?
あ！
Oh!
はい、ホロスターズ1期生の律可です。よろしくお願いします！
All right! I'm Rikka from Holostars 1st Generation. Glad to be here!
うぉー！イェーイ！
Woo! Yay!
じゃあ次は？
Who's next?
はい！ホロスターズUPROAR!!の水無世燐央でーす！よろしくお願いします！
Hi! I'm Minase Rio from Holostars UPROAR!! Pleased to meet you!
よろしく！
Welcome!
イェーイ！
Yay!
イオフィ、一緒に歌ってくれてありがとう。本当に。
Iofi, thank you so much for singing with us. Truly.
いや、こちらこそ！呼んでくれてありがとう！
No, the pleasure is ours! Thank you for inviting us!
いやー、嬉しかった！ありがとうございました！
Man, I was so happy! Thank you so much!
ね！
Right!
なんか、律可パイセンからは、私がデビューの頃結構、お世話になってて、私が。
Actually, Rikka-paisan really took good care of me when I just debuted.
1対1のコラボとか来てもらったりしたもんね。
Yeah, we did some 1-on-1 collabs together back then.
そうそう！
Yeah, exactly!
なので、なんか今回歌いたいなと思って。
So I really wanted to sing with you this time.
おお,ありがとうね。
Oh, thank you.
来てくれてありがとう。
Thanks for coming.
で、リオくんは…
And as for Rio-kun...
リオ、リオは？
What about Rio?
リオくんは、あははは！
Rio-kun is... *laughs*
後輩だもんね。後輩。
He's a junior, after all.
後輩！そうそうそうそう！
A junior! Yeah, exactly!
なんか、スタジオで会った時にさ、あの仕事で、たまたまあの、キラッ…キラッ…？
We happened to bump into each other at a studio for work, and...
なんかこう、
he was like,
「じゃあ、次の来年の誕生日にさ、あの、来てくれる？」って。
"So, will you come to my next birthday live?"
そう、言ってくれて。スタジオで本当にばったり会って。
Yeah, he said that! We really just ran into each other at the studio.
ばったり会って、そう。言ってくれて。
We just bumped into each other, and he asked me.
まさか本当に呼んでくれると思わなくて。
I never expected you'd actually invite me!
え、逆に信じてなかったの！？
Wait, you didn't believe me?!
違う違う違う！
No, no, no!
もう、嬉しすぎてびっくりしちゃったよ僕。ありがとうございます！
I was just so incredibly happy and surprised. Thank you so much!
ううん、いいよ、いいよ、ありがとう！
No, no, not at all! Thank you!
ありがとうございました！
Thank you so much!
え、私たち揃うのが、
Wait, the three of us gathering like this...
2年ぶりだっけ？
Is it after two years?
久しぶりだよね。そう、2年前！
It's been a while. Yeah, two years ago!
ライブ！
The live!
ホロスターズサイドのカウントダウンライブで、あのこの3人とコボちゃんと4人で歌わせていただいたんですけど。
At the Holostars Countdown Live, the three of us and Kobo-chan, the four of us sang together.
一緒に歌うのはね、実はそれぶり。
But singing with just the three of us is actually a first since then.
それぶり。
Since then.
だいぶ久しぶり。
It's been quite a while.
2年前？そっか、もう2年経った？
Two years ago? Oh, has it really been two years?
そう、2年経ったんだな。
Yeah, two years have passed.
2年経ったなー、って感じ。
It really feels like two years.
早いなー。
Time flies.
早い。
So fast.
早いです。一緒に歌えてめちゃくちゃ楽しかったです！
It really is. Singing together was so much fun!
え、ありがとう！本当？
Oh, thank you! Really?
いや、なんか3人バンドみたいだった。
Yeah, it felt like we were a three-piece band.
ギター1人、ボーカル2人みたいな。
With one guitar and two vocalists.
見たことある感じの絵面だった。
It was a scene we've seen somewhere before.
来年だったらもうバンドやりますよ、そしたら。
If so, let's form a proper band next year!
バンドね。
A band, huh?
じゃあ、僕ドラムやろうかな。
Then, maybe I'll play the drums.
ドラム？
Drums?
ドラムやる？
You'll play drums?
そしたらなんかいい感じになる。じゃあ俺、トライアングルやるわ。
That would be nice. Then I'll play the triangle.
あれ、なんで？
Wait, why?!
何やる？
What will you play?
マラカス。
Maracas.
リズムいらないでしょ！
We don't need that much rhythm!
リズム隊じゃん！
That's just a rhythm section!
音聞こえないけど。
We won't hear much else.
ギターとかいないんだ。
So there's no guitar anymore.
だってトライアングルとか思わなかった、こう、チーンってするだけでしょ。
I didn't expect a triangle, just going "ding" like that.
気持ちいいよね、一発。
But that one ding feels great, you know?
タンバリンにしようかな。
Maybe I'll do tambourine.
気持ちいい。
Feels good.
タンバリンね。
Tambourine, huh?
タンバリンで、
Tambourine rhythm.
みんなうるさい奴じゃん、シャカシャカシャカシャカ。
Everyone's just playing noisy instruments.
結構しっとりだったから。
Since the song was quite gentle.
確かに。
Indeed.
誰かわかんないですけど、流石にこれはね。
I don't know who, but indeed we should do this.
ハモリ難しかったね、やっぱり。
The harmony was quite difficult, as expected.
3人だからさ。
Since there are three of us.
そう。なんか元々、男性と女性がなんか二人で歌う曲見つけるのちょっと、結構難しくて。
Yeah. Originally, finding a song for a male and female to sing together is actually quite difficult.
確かにね、キーがね。
True, because of the keys.
キーが、でも女性の曲だったらキー下げなきゃいけないし、
If it's a female song, we have to lower the key,
男性のだったら、こっちが低すぎるし。
and if it's a male song, it's too low for me.
だからどうしようと思って。
So I was wondering what to do.
めちゃめちゃ素敵な曲。
It's a really wonderful song.
ね、ハモリもすごく良かった。
Yeah, the harmony was great too.
ありがとう、良かった。
Thank you, I'm glad.
ありがとう。
Thank you.
うん、なんかゲストは…
Yeah, the guests...
最初のには、やっぱり絶対にリオくんと律可パイセンを招待したいんだけど、その時期に曲まだ決まってなくて。
At first, I absolutely wanted to invite Rio-kun and Rikka-paisan, but at that time, the song wasn't decided yet.
あ、そうなんだ！
Oh, is that so!
後から決まった。
It was decided later.
後から、そう、後から。
Later on, yeah, later on.
いいの見つかったね。
We found a good one, though.
ありがとう、本当に良かったよ！
Thank you, I'm really glad we did!
声も合ってたし、この3人の。めちゃめちゃ良かった。
Our voices blended well together, the three of us. It was so good.
いやでもまたやりたいけどね / え、やりたい
Well, I'd love to do this again sometime. / Yeah, me too!
...が終わった
That's over.
ねえ、次はバンド？
Hey, is a band next?
バンドやる？バンドやるか
Do a band? Shall we?
バンド、マラカス
Band? I'll do maracas.
練習時間めっちゃかかりそうだけど
That seems like it would take a lot of practice.
確かに。ドラムやったことないからな
True, I've never played drums before.
何やるの？ 叩くしかない
What are you doing? I can only beat them!
やるなら練習しますよ
If we're doing it, we'll practice!
あ、じゃあ来年やります、バンド
Then we'll do a band next year!
楽しみに。多分、多分
Look forward to it. Maybe, maybe!
本当にやりそうだからな。怖い
They might actually do it! Scary!
ということで来年楽しみに...
So, look forward to next year...
みんな本気にするよ、これ、みんな本気にするよ
Everyone will take this seriously, you know!
怖い、怖い
Scary, scary!
じゃあ、来年お楽しみにということで！
So, look forward to next year!
はい！
Yes!
見てくれてありがとう！これからもね、まだまだあるので
Thank you for watching! There's still more,
楽しんでください！
so please enjoy!
はい、楽しんで！
Yes, enjoy!
楽しんでね！おめでとう！ありがとう！
Enjoy! Congratulations! Thank you!
楽しんでね！
Enjoy!
ぼくらのレッドイットビー
[Title: Our Let It Bee]
生まれ変われるのなら
If we can be reborn,
目印になるから 巻いとこう
I'll make a mark, so let's wind it up.
小指と小指の長い糸
Little finger to little finger, the long thread,
ほどけない様に 結んどこう
let's tie it so it won't untie.
夏祭り りんご飴
Summer festival, candy apple,
雨降り 空に 虹が架かる頃なの
when a rainbow arches across the rainy sky.
壊れた感情が いつか 君を消していく
Broken emotions will someday erase you,
見えなくなると 失われる灯火
a light that is lost when it becomes invisible.
でも 結んだ長い糸 ほどけ落ちていないから
But the long thread we tied hasn't fallen untied,
また ぼくたちは 出会う時が来る きっと
so surely, the time for us to meet again will come.
ぼくら おとなになったら
When we grow up,
せいぎのヒーローになるんだ
we'll become heroes of justice.
地球の平和を守るのさ
To protect the peace of the Earth!
探検しようぜ おばけ屋敷
Let's explore the haunted house.
でもほんとうは こわくって なきむし
Even though I'm actually scared, a crybaby,
一緒にいたいだけ
I just want to be together.
明日も晴れて 空を 青く照らせば
If tomorrow is sunny too, and shines blue upon the sky,
ぼくらは ここに ひみつきちを作ろう
we'll build a secret base here,
そして 探検しよう 雨ならゲームをしよう
and explore. If it rains, let's play games.
そんな時間が ずっと 続くはずだったんだ
Such a time was supposed to last forever.
そう
Yes.
わるものは ぼくだった
The villain was me.
逃げたのは ぼくだ
The one who ran away was me.
嘘じゃない 本当の嘘つきだ
It's no lie, I'm a real liar.
花束に 包まれて
Wrapped in a bouquet of flowers,
目を瞑る君は
closing your eyes, you
安らかに 清らかに 眠っていたんだ
were sleeping peacefully, purely.
壊れた感情が いつか 君を消していく
Broken emotions will someday erase you,
失う前に 消えてしまう前に
before losing you, before you disappear,
まだ 結んだ長い糸 ほどけ落ちていなかった
the long thread we tied still hadn't fallen untied.
きっと ぼくたちは
Surely, we...
...harus kuingat selalu
...I must always remember
...pasti...
...for sure...
[Title: Pandangan Pertama]
[Title: First Sight]
Lama ku memendam rasa di dada
For a long time, I've kept this feeling inside my chest
Mengagumi indahmu wahai jelita
Admiring your beauty, oh gorgeous one
Tak dapat lagi kuucap kata
I can no longer speak a word
Bisaku diam terpesona
Speechless, I stand in awe
Dan andai suatu hari kau jadi milikku
And if one day you become mine
Tak akan kulepas dirimu oh kasih
I will never let you go, oh my love
Dan bila waktu mengizinkanku untuk menunggu
And if time allows me to wait
dirimu...
for you...
Kurasa ku telah jatuh cinta
I think I've fallen in love
Pada pandangan yang pertama
At first sight
Sulit bagiku untuk bisa
It's hard for me to be able to
Berhenti mengagumi dirinya
Stop admiring her
Seiring dengan berjalannya waktu
Along with the passage of time
Akhirnya kita berdua bertemu
Finally, we two met
Oh diriku tersipu malu
Oh, I blushed with shyness
Melihat sikapmu yang lucu
Seeing your funny attitude
Dan andai suatu hari kau jadi milikku
And if one day you become mine
Tak akan kulepas dirimu oh kasih
I will never let you go, oh my love
Dan bila waktu mengizinkanku menunggu
And if time allows me to wait
dirimu...
for you...
Kurasa ku telah jatuh cinta
I think I've fallen in love
Pada pandangan yang pertama
At first sight
Sulit bagiku untuk bisa
It's hard for me to be able to
Berhenti mengagumi dirinya
Stop admiring her
Oh Tuhan tolonglah diriku
Oh God, please help me
Tuk membuat dia menjadi milikku
To make her mine
Sayangku, kasihku, oh cintaku
My darling, my love, oh my sweetheart
She's all that I need
Dan bila kita bersama
And when we are together
Kan kujaga dirimu untuk selamanya
I'll watch over you forever
Oh terima cintaku
Oh, accept my love
Summertime, ain't a summertime
If I don't have you as mine, but you're always on my mind, yeah
In the magazine you showed up
Baby girl, your beauty makes my mind blow up
Your personality, it's calm and friendly
The kinda girl that I would love to be with me
Once I start, no, I won't fall back
Here's my cell phone number, so please call back, come on!
Kurasa ku telah jatuh cinta
I think I've fallen in love
Pada pandangan yang pertama
At first sight
Sulit bagiku untuk bisa
It's hard for me to be able to
Berhenti mengagumi dirinya
Stop admiring her
Oh Tuhan tolonglah diriku
Oh God, please help me
Tuk membuat dia menjadi milikku
To make her mine
Sayangku, kasihku, oh cintaku
My darling, my love, oh my sweetheart
She's all that I need
Pesawat Kertas 365 Hari
[Title: 365 Days of Paper Airplanes]
Ku tatap langit di pagi hari
I look up at the morning sky
Ku awali hari dengan doa
Starting my day with a prayer
Semoga satu hari ini bisa...
Hoping that today can be...
...dipenuhi oleh senyum
...filled with smiles
Walaupun terkadang hujan turun
Even if it sometimes rains
Dan air mata juga mengalir
And the tears begin to flow
Di hari yang tak berjalan dengan mulus
On days that don't go smoothly
Besok pun tetap semangat
I'll still keep my spirits up tomorrow
Di dalam mimpiku selalu...
In my dreams, I always...
...terlihat ada diriku sendiri
...see myself standing there
Yang dengan bebasnya melakukan semua...
Freely doing whatever...
...hal yang ingin aku lakukan
...it is that I want to do
Hidup bagaikan pesawat kertas
Life is like a paper airplane
Terbang dan pergi membawa impian
Flying and soaring with our dreams
Sekuat tenaga dengan hembusan angin
With all its might against the blowing wind
Terus melaju terbang
It continues to speed ahead
Jangan bandingkan jarak terbangnya
Don't compare how far it flies
Tapi bagaimana dan apa yang dilalui
But how and what it went through
Karena itulah satu hal yang penting
Because that is the one important thing
Selalu sesuai kata hati
Always follow your heart
Sanbyaku rokujūgo nichi
365 days
Di saat terlihat bintang-bintang
When the stars are visible
Atau malam yang gelap gulita
Or on a pitch-black night
Pada saat semangatmu hilang carilah...
When you lose your spirit, look for...
...orang lain dan bicara
...someone else and talk to them
Manusia tidaklah pernah...
Humans are never...
...ditinggal sendirian saja
...left entirely all alone
Terkadang kita tak menyadari
Sometimes we don't realize
Hal baik di sekitar kita
The good things around us
Hidup bagaikan pesawat kertas
Life is like a paper airplane
Terbang dan membawa cinta kita semua
Flying and carrying the love of us all
Sayap yang terbentang dengan percaya diri
Wings spread out with confidence
Dilihat semua orang
Watched by everyone
Walau tak tahu cara melipatnya
Even if you don't know how to fold it
Suatu saat pasti akan berhasil lalu terbang
One day, it will surely succeed and fly
Kekuatan harapan yang menerbangkannya
The power of hope that makes it fly
Ya mari nikmatilah
Yes, let's just enjoy it
Sanbyaku rokujūgo nichi
365 days
Hidup bagaikan pesawat kertas
Life is like a paper airplane
Terbang dan pergi membawa impian
Flying and soaring with our dreams
Sekuat tenaga dengan hembusan angin
With all its might against the blowing wind
Terus melaju terbang
It continues to speed ahead
Jangan bandingkan jarak terbangnya
Don't compare how far it flies
Tapi bagaimana dan apa yang dilalui
But how and what it went through
Karena itulah satu hal yang penting
Because that is the one important thing
Selalu sesuai kata hati
Always follow your heart
Sanbyaku rokujūgo nichi
365 days
Ayo terbanglah! (Coba terbanglah!)
Come on, fly! (Give it a try and fly!)
...lah
...fly away
Ayo terbanglah
Come on, fly away!
Coba terbanglah
Try to fly away!
Ayo terbanglah
Come on, fly away!
Coba terbanglah
Try to fly away!
Whoa! Akhirnya!
Whoa! Finally!
Yey! Halo semuanya!
Yay! Hello everyone!
Oh my God, lu lihat gue dong.
Oh my God, look at me!
Hi, Iofi! Hi, Pia.
Akhirnya ya Pia, kolab kecil-kecilan kita nggak kecil, udah jadi besar, guys!
Finally, Pia, our small collaboration isn't small anymore. It has grown big, guys!
Yay!
Finally!
Terima kasih... Uhuk, ini berdebu.
Thank you... *cough*, it's dusty here.
Terima kasih sudah mengundang saya, Senpai.
Thank you for inviting me, Senpai.
Woy, Senpai!
Hey, Senpai!
Ulang tahun yang keberapa, Senpai?
Which anniversary is this, Senpai?
Enam!
Six!
Tapi kok belum lulus-lulus juga?
But why haven't you graduated yet?
Daripada gitu, mending jikoshoukai dulu.
Instead of that, let's introduce ourselves first.
We are on fire!
Selamat malam bara yang menghangatkan hari-harimu!
Good evening, embers that warm up your days!
Halo, aku Pia Meraleo dari JKT48 Virtual generasi pertama! Halo semuanya, malam!
Hello, I am Pia Meraleo from JKT48 Virtual 1st Generation! Hello everyone, good evening!
Malam!
Good evening!
Oh my God, yes.
By the way, aku nyadar sesuatu tahu nggak.
By the way, I realized something.
Apa?
What?
Sorry, so basically buat kalian yang bilang aku lebih pendek...
Sorry, so basically for those of you who said I'm shorter...
Now, you guys see?
Halah, dikit doang.
Geez, just a little bit.
Dikit doang means everything to me, you know!
Just a little bit means everything to me, you know!
No, no, no, senyonya doang. Heels-mu berapa?
No, no, no, just a tiny bit. How high are your heels?
Ah, oke, duduk aja yuk.
Ah, okay, let's just sit down.
Well, for your information, nggak banyak sih, paling 18 cm.
Well, for your information, not much, maybe 18 cm.
Tapi tapi aslinya kaki aku nggak nyampe.
But but in reality, my feet don't touch the ground.
See? Dia dia tuh emang...
See? She is indeed...
Look at that! Ngambang, cuy! Kaki kita ngambang for no reason! Kaki gua!
Look at that! It's floating, dude! Our feet are floating for no reason! My feet!
Kaki gua nggak nyampe.
My feet don't reach.
Beda ya, beda.
It's different, indeed.
Lihat ini! Lihat!
Look at this! Look!
Kaki Pia nggak nyampe.
Pia's feet don't reach.
Okelah. Oh my God. Jadi, ya, lagu ini ya...
Okay then. Oh my God. So, yeah, this song...
By the way, koreografinya Ritsuke-nee...
By the way, the choreography is by Ritsuke-nee...
Aku dikasih tahu sama Pia. Pia-kara oshiete moratta.
Pia told me. Pia taught me.
Hahaha, iya, begitu.
Hahaha, yes, that's right.
Itu favorit banget, kan?
That's a huge favorite, right?
Coba sekali lagi, gimana, gimana?
Let's try one more time, how does it go?
Tanatana~
Mantap, kawai.
Awesome, cute.
Kawai, imut banget, kan?
Cute, so cute, right?
Asyik, asyik. Iya, jadi gitu.
Nice, nice. Yes, so that's it.
Guys, tolong don't judge me. Don't judge me! We are learning, okay? We are learning.
Guys, please don't judge me. Don't judge me! We are learning, okay? We are learning.
We are learning.
Jadi kalau ada yang apa-apa-apa ya ke Pia.
So if there is anything, blame Pia.
Nggak gitu ya! Nggak gitu!
It doesn't work that way! No!
Anyway, what is this?
Karena kamu mau ke sini, aku prepare ini.
Since you wanted to come here, I prepared this.
Really? Is this like for me? Yes, coba-coba.
Really? Is this like for me? Yes, try it.
Dideketin kayak gimana?
How do we get closer to it?
We are on fire!
Aku anget banget, guys.
I feel so warm, guys.
*sniff* Bau gue.
*sniff* It smells like me.
Jadi kalau kalian penasaran baunya Pia kayak gimana, kayak gini, guys.
So if you guys are curious what Pia smells like, it's like this, guys.
Bau arang, bau abu, bau arang itu bau gue, cuy.
Charcoal smell, ash smell, charcoal smell is my smell, dude.
Ini lucu banget.
This is so cute.
Oh my God, kore wa...
Oh my God, this is...
Nggak mau pulang boleh nggak?
Can I not go home, please?
Gue di sini jadi tukang kabel juga nggak apa-apa deh.
I'm fine even if I stay here to manage the cables.
Serius deh.
Seriously.
Tapi iya, terima kasih ya untuk manager-nya Pia sudah apa meminjamkan saya Pia.
But yes, thank you to Pia's manager for lending me Pia.
M-chan, arigatou. Buat staff-staff, M-chan, arigatou.
M-chan, thank you. To all the staff and M-chan, thank you.
Arigatou.
Thank you.
Yeah, oh my God, I cannot really... Oh my God, oshiku.
Yeah, oh my God, I really can't... Oh my God, my oshi.
Akhirnya aku bisa manggil kamu tuh...
Finally I can call you...
Aku tuh, guys, waktu pertama kali dibilang aku mau invite kamu, aku kayak...
Guys, when I was first told that I was going to invite you, I was like...
Nani?!
What?!
Terus manager-ku kayak, kalau bisa kupegang, kayak...
And my manager was like, if only I could hold you, like...
Aku diundang sama oshiku!
I got invited by my oshi!
Iya, begitu. Tapi ya...
Yes, indeed. But yeah...
Tapi aku walaupun excited harus pulang, bro.
But although I'm excited, I have to go home, bro.
Oh, iya bener.
Oh, right.
Thank you for coming, Pia, arigatou.
Thank you for coming, Pia, thank you.
Yeah, thank you. You know, enjoy the rest of the show.
I will watch from there.
I will watch from over there.
Okay, see you. Cepat-cepat.
Okay, see you. Hurry back.
Bye-bye! Arigatou! Thank you!
Bye-bye! Thank you! Thank you!
Yohorya! Oh, bisa! Kita sudah di penghujung acara nih, guys!
Yohorya! Oh, we can! We are already at the end of the show, guys!
Tapi sebelum kita ke akhir acara, aku mau berterima kasih dulu.
But before we reach the end of the show, I'd like to say thank you first.
Terima kasih sudah datang. Muah! Toranei-sama, arigatou. Decapas-sama, arigatou.
Thank you for coming. Muah! Toranei-sama, thank you. Decapas-sama, thank you.
Ryo-kun, arigatou. Pia juga terima kasih. Dan Ritsu-dono...
Ryo-kun, thank you. Thank you to Pia too. And Ritsu-dono...
みんな、ありがとう、みんな！
Thank you, everyone!
いや、やっとね、イオフィ1st... 誕生日、誕生日記念2025も終盤となりました。
Yes, finally, Iofi's birthday celebration 2025 is reaching its end.
Tapi jangan skip ads dulu! Sebelum berakhir, aku punya sesuatu untuk kalian.
But don't skip the ads just yet! Before it ends, I have something for you.
Tengok! Birthday goods-nya... tada! Boom!
Look! The birthday goods... tada! Boom!
Hai! Iofi Birthday 2025. Kita punya tiga merch dan sesuatu yang spesial, dan voice. Mari kita lihat, ya! Tonton!
Yes! Iofi Birthday 2025. We have three merch items, something special, and a voice pack. Let's take a look! Tada!
ioDreaming Blanket!
イオフィは24/7、イオフィが暖かく包んであげるよ。こうやってギュッとね。暖かいからね。
Iofi is here 24/7, Iofi will wrap you up warmly. Like this, tight! Because it's warm.
Nah, jadi kalau kalian, aduh, dingin, perlu ditemani hangat, ini aku akan menemani malam-malammu yang dingin.
So if you're cold and need some warm company, I will accompany you through the cold nights.
で、今年もイラストは夜みつきママ！ありがとう！皆さんのママもありがとう！はい！
And this year's illustration is also by Mitsuki-mama! Thank you! Thank you, everyone's mama! Yes!
Lucu sekali, fuwa-fuwa, kawaii.
It's so cute, fluffy, and lovely.
Eh, tapi kalau udah ada blanket berarti kurang apa, sih? Nah, next up!
But if you already have a blanket, what else are you missing? Well, next up!
We have this one! Sweet Dreams Pillow Cover!
Jadi ini selain... mmm... tapi kayaknya kepala kalian bisa pas buat di... ehem...
So besides this... mmm... I think your head would fit perfectly right... *cough*...
Basically, it's so fuwa-fuwa, it's so comfy. You can place your head right in... yeah.
Basically, it's so fluffy, it's so comfy. You can place your head right in... yeah.
あの、これ良いですよ。こうやって、はぁ、そうそう。あっ、でもでもでも...
You know, this is really nice. Like this, ah, yes, yes. Ah, but, but, but...
イオフィに夢中すぎて、ちょっと時間忘れてちゃう！あ、やばいどうしよう！っていう時は、こちらです！
I'm so crazy about Iofi that I forgot the time! Oh no, what should I do! In times like that, here is this!
Dreaming Palette Acrylic Clock.
Jadi kalian kalau punya ini nggak akan lupa waktu. "Aduh, aku terlalu fokus sama Iofi, aku lupa waktu. Oh my God!" Ini!
So if you have this, you won't forget the time. "Oh no, I'm too focused on Iofi, I forgot the time! Oh my God!" This!
So you won't really forget about time while thinking about me.
Cute, kan?
Cute, right?
あっ、でもでもでも、次、次、次は...何々？あっ、こちらです！はい、どうぞ！
Ah, but, but, but, next, next, next is... what is it? Ah, here it is! Yes, please!
Voice Pack!
Jadi ini kita bisa ketemu di dalam mimpi, "Dream Rendezvous". So you will be meeting me in a dream. So, 夢でも会えるように、このボイスを聞いてね！はい！
With this, we can meet in a dream, "Dream Rendezvous". So you will be meeting me in a dream. So please listen to this voice pack so we can meet in your dreams too! Yes!
では、日本語、インドネシア語と英語、3つです！はい、全部聞いてね！
And we have Japanese, Indonesian, and English—all three! Yes, please listen to all of them!
で、今年は新しいの、珍しいのが出てくるのよ！There's gonna be something new this year, and this is it!
And this year, something new and rare is coming out! There's gonna be something new this year, and this is it!
Bam!
If you buy the full set, there's gonna be Hololive Card Game!
If you buy the full set, there's gonna be a Hololive Card Game!
This is a bonus Hololive card! This comes as a bonus for purchasing the premium full set...
Premium merchandise, akan tambahan bonus kartu yang bisa kalian pakai di gamenya Official Hololive, guys! Yes!
Premium merchandise! You'll get an additional bonus card that you can use in the official Hololive Card Game, guys! Yes!
You can actually use it on the, on the game, ya!
You can actually use it in the game!
これでさ、大会とかで使ったらさ、めっちゃ自慢できますよ。こうやって、「うわ！これがイオフィの限定の誕生日グッズから出たやつ！」
With this, if you use it in tournaments, you can really show it off. Like, "Whoa! This is the one from Iofi's limited birthday merchandise!"
でも、お守りとしてもね、ここに置いてても大丈夫ですよ。イオフィがここにいるから。
But even as a good luck charm, it's fine to keep it near. Because Iofi is here.
Iya, jadi ini bonus bisa dipakai di kartu, ya, di gamenya Official Hololive Card, tapi kartunya hari ini yang ini sayang sekali baru ada bahasa Jepangnya, jadi mohon pengertiannya, ya.
Yes, so this card can be used in the official Hololive Card Game. But unfortunately, this card is currently only available in Japanese, so we appreciate your understanding.
Untuk detail kartu dan cara bermain, bisa dicek di homepage. Begitu, guys, terima kasih!
For card details and how to play, you can check the official homepage. That's all, guys, thank you!
Dan kita sudah sampai di penghujung... acara.
And we have arrived at the very end... of the event.
Hmm, jadi karena tahun lalu kita udah dengar "Here I Am" yang biasa, nah tahun ini aku punya yang spesial untuk kalian.
Since last year we listened to the regular "Here I Am", this year I have something special for you.
Here I Am full Bahasa Indonesia!
Here I Am full Indonesian version!
Ah! Here I Am Indonesian version!
Tapi itu hanya untuk membership, ya, メンバー限定で"Here I Am"インドネシア語バージョン、後で歌います。はい！
But that's only for membership. I'll sing the Indonesian version of "Here I Am" later, exclusive for members. Yes!
Jadi habis ini akan... apa ya, aku akan ketemu kalian di membership, oke?
So after this, I'll meet you guys in the membership stream, okay?
では、本当の本当の本当の最後の曲になります。はい、this will be my last song for tonight!
Now, this is truly, truly the very last song. Yes, this will be my last song for tonight!
I hope you are ready.
This last song will be... 「心の坂道」、手話で。
This last song will be... "Kokoro no Sakamichi", in sign language.
何度も苦しい思いをした
I've been through pain more times than I can say
何度も哀しい思いをした
I've felt the sorrow that wouldn't go away
今日までたくさん歩いてきた
Step by step, I've made it here today
心の坂道を
Up the hill where my feelings lay
歩き慣れた帰り道で 突然転んだ
I tripped and fell on the road I always take
不意打ちみたいで まるで
Caught off guard, like a sudden break
後ろから刺された気分
It hit me like a stab in the back
…るんだ
破けたジーンズと
In torn-up jeans
心の隙間に
and a heart with a crack,
冷たい風が抜ける
The cold wind gently passes through
小石蹴飛ばして
I kick a pebble as I move on too
一歩踏み出すとき
The moment I took a single step ahead,
君がいてくれた
I found you standing there instead
何度も苦しい思いをした
I've been through pain more times than I can say
何度も哀しい思いもした
I've felt the sorrow that wouldn't go away
今日までたくさん歩いてきた
Step by step, I've made it here today
心の坂道は
Up the hill where my feelings lay
君がいたから強くなれた
Because you were there for me, I found the strength to be
傷だらけで歩いた坂もあるいた
Even with scars, I climbed that hill with ease
君がいるから歩いていけるさ
Because you're here with me, I know I'll keep walking free
涙の足跡残さないで
Leaving no tears for the world to see
あの日君は言っていた
That day, you said to me
本当の強さは
True strength
泣いてもまた笑えることだよ
is being able to cry, then smile again, you know?
何度も苦しい思いをした
I've been through pain more times than I can say
何度も哀しい思いもした
I've felt the sorrow that wouldn't go away
今日までたくさん歩いてきた
Step by step, I've made it here today
心の坂道は
Up the hill where my feelings lay
君がいたから強くなれた
Because you were there for me, I found the strength to be
傷だらけで歩いた坂もあるいた
Even with scars, I climbed that hill with ease
君がいるから歩いていけるさ
Because you're here with me, I know I'll keep walking free
涙の足跡残さないで
Leaving no tears for the world to see
君がいたから
Because you were there for me
君がいるから
Because you're here with me